[
  {
    "front": "What type of bridge is the Golden Gate Bridge?",
    "back": "Suspension"
  },
  {
    "front": "The dingo is a free ranging dog found mainly in which country?",
    "back": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "front": "Which painter started the impressionist movement?",
    "back": "Claude Monet"
  },
  {
    "front": "What is the Japanese word that means 'empty orchestra'?",
    "back": "Karaoke"
  },
  {
    "front": "War and Peace, originally published in 1869, is a novel written by which Russian author?",
    "back": "Leo Tolstoy"
  },
  {
    "front": "What does HTTP stand for in a website address?",
    "back": "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol"
  },
  {
    "front": "Which country won the 2012 UEFA European Championship?",
    "back": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "front": "Released in 1992, what is the best selling soundtrack album of all time?",
    "back": "The Bodyguard"
  },
  {
    "front": "Who played the female lead in the 1942 film Casablanca?",
    "back": "Ingrid Bergman"
  },
  {
    "front": "In the 'Lord of the Rings' film series which actor plays the character of Saruman?",
    "back": "Christopher Lee"
  },
  {
    "front": "Who owns the Detroit Red Wings hockey team?",
    "back": "Mike Illitch"
  },
  {
    "front": "Who?",
    "back": "The Who"
  }
]